<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="MCQs">
        <item >Trout, carp and, barracuda are names of what?</item>
        <item >How many consonants are there in the English alphabet?</item>
        <item > What body part grows quicker?</item>
        <item >Which is the tallest mountain in the world?</item>
        <item > Which Saint’s Day is celebrated on 14th February?</item>
        <item >Which famous children’s book has two characters named Tweedledum and Tweedledee?</item>
        <item >Which planet is known as the Red Planet?</item>
        <item >Place these shapes in order of how many sides they have—square, triangle, octagon, and hexagon?</item>
        <item >Which of the following is not a metal?</item>
        <item > Which is the largest plateau in the world?</item>
        <item >In which ocean did the famous Titanic sink in 1912?</item>
        <item >What is the next number in the following sequence– 7, 14, 21, 28?</item>
        <item >Which two parts of the body continue to grow for your entire life?</item>
        <item >What makes up (approx.) 80% of our brain’s volume?</item>
        <item > Which country does volleyball originate from?</item>
        <item > What is Zumba?</item>
        <item >What is the temperature of moon during the day?</item>
        <item >Which planet is the smallest:Earth,Neptune, Mars, Mercury?</item>
        <item >What is the square root of 144?</item>
        <item >What is three-fifths of 50?</item>
        <item >During which year did World War I begin?</item>
        <item >Which famous explorer discovered Cuba?</item>
        <item >What type of whale is the biggest animal in the world?</item>
        <item >Who was nicknamed “Trey” (Three in card terminology), when he was young?</item>
        <item >Which first electrical item did Thomas Edison invent?</item>
        <item >How many players are there in an ice hockey team?</item>
        <item >Which instrument is used for measuring wind speed?</item>
        <item >How many straight edges does a cube have?</item>
        <item >Which layer of planet Earth is made up of tectonic plates?</item>
        <item >Can you name the legendary Benedictine monk who invented champagne?</item>
        <item >Which kind of ‘bulbs’ were once exchanged as a form of currency?</item>
        <item >What does the term ‘Piano’ mean?</item>
        <item > What kind of weapon is a falchion?</item>
        <item >What is another word for a ‘lexicon’?</item>
        <item >In football (soccer), who was nicknamed ‘The Divine Ponytail’?</item>
        <item >How many cards are there in a complete pack of cards?</item>
        <item > What is the hottest continent on Earth?</item>
        <item >What is the most popular sport throughout the world?</item>
        <item >Can you name the country from where Parmesan cheese comes?</item>
        <item >What type of tree do dates grow on?</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>